let questions8 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to accept",
        answer: "A. akzeptieren",
        options: [
            "A. akzeptieren",
            "B. ablehnen",
            "C. stornieren",
            "D. ankündigen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to arrange",
        answer: "B. arrangieren",
        options: [
            "A. durcheinanderbringen",
            "B. arrangieren",
            "C. stornieren",
            "D. ändern"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "to attend",
        answer: "A. teilnehmen",
        options: [
            "A. teilnehmen",
            "B. besuchen",
            "C. ignorieren",
            "D. vergessen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to balance",
        answer: "C. balancieren",
        options: [
            "A. entsprechen",
            "B. verändern",
            "C. balancieren",
            "D. unterstützen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "contrast",
        answer: "D. Kontrast",
        options: [
            "A. Ähnlichkeit",
            "B. Gleichheit",
            "C. Gemeinsamkeit",
            "D. Kontrast"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to encourage",
        answer: "A. ermutigen",
        options: [
            "A. ermutigen",
            "B. kritisieren",
            "C. verhindern",
            "D. ignorieren"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "familiar",
        answer: "B. vertraut",
        options: [
            "A. Familie",
            "B. vertraut",
            "C. neu",
            "D. fremd"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "to grab",
        answer: "C. greifen",
        options: [
            "A. werfen",
            "B. geben",
            "C. greifen",
            "D. ändern"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to hang",
        answer: "A. hängen",
        options: [
            "A. hängen",
            "B. legen",
            "C. aufstellen",
            "D. heben"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "huge",
        answer: "D. riesig",
        options: [
            "A. klein",
            "B. mittelgroß",
            "C. eng",
            "D. riesig"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "necessary",
        answer: "B. notwendig",
        options: [
            "A. überflüssig",
            "B. notwendig",
            "C. freiwillig",
            "D. obligatorisch"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "pattern",
        answer: "C. Muster",
        options: [
            "A. Prozess",
            "B. Empfehlung",
            "C. Muster",
            "D. Methode"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "to propose",
        answer: "B. vorschlagen",
        options: [
            "A. beraten",
            "B. vorschlagen",
            "C. tadeln",
            "D. leugnen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "purpose",
        answer: "A. Zweck",
        options: [
            "A. Zweck",
            "B. Zufall",
            "C. Wunsch",
            "D. Traum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to release",
        answer: "B. freilassen",
        options: [
            "A. festhalten",
            "B. freilassen",
            "C. einsperren",
            "D. einschränken"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to require",
        answer: "C. erfordern",
        options: [
            "A. einführen",
            "B. mitteilen",
            "C. erfordern",
            "D. verbieten"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "single",
        answer: "D. einzeln",
        options: [
            "A. wenige",
            "B. mehrere",
            "C. fremd",
            "D. einzeln"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "success",
        answer: "A. Erfolg",
        options: [
            "A. Erfolg",
            "B. Glück",
            "C. Freude",
            "D. Zufriedenheit"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to tear",
        answer: "B. zerreißen",
        options: [
            "A. nähen",
            "B. zerreißen",
            "C. verbinden",
            "D. kleben"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "theory",
        answer: "C. Theorie",
        options: [
            "A. Praxis",
            "B. Zustand",
            "C. Theorie",
            "D. Experiment"
        ]
    }
];
